spine_and_trunk_oian_quiz = [
    {"question": "What is the origin of Rectus Abdominis?", "options": ["Pubic crest and symphysis", "Iliac crest", "Costal cartilages of ribs 5-7"], "answer": "a"},
    {"question": "What is the insertion of Rectus Abdominis?", "options": ["Xiphoid process and costal cartilages of ribs 5-7", "Pubic crest and symphysis", "Iliac crest"], "answer": "a"},
    {"question": "What is the action of Rectus Abdominis?", "options": ["Extends vertebral column", "Flexes vertebral column", "Rotates vertebral column"], "answer": "b"},
    {"question": "What is the nerve of Rectus Abdominis?", "options": ["Intercostal nerves", "Femoral nerve", "Thoracoabdominal nerves"], "answer": "c"},
    {"question": "What is the origin of Erector Spinae?", "options": ["Iliac crest, sacrum, and lumbar vertebrae", "Pubic crest and symphysis", "Xiphoid process and costal cartilages of ribs 5-7"], "answer": "a"},
    {"question": "What is the insertion of Erector Spinae?", "options": ["Transverse processes of thoracic and cervical vertebrae", "Spinous processes of lumbar vertebrae", "Iliac crest"], "answer": "a"},
    {"question": "What is the action of Erector Spinae?", "options": ["Flexes vertebral column", "Rotates vertebral column", "Extends vertebral column"], "answer": "c"},
    {"question": "What is the nerve of Erector Spinae?", "options": ["Dorsal rami of spinal nerves", "Femoral nerve", "Thoracoabdominal nerves"], "answer": "a"},
    {"question": "What is the origin of External Oblique?", "options": ["Lower eight ribs", "Iliac crest", "Pubic crest and symphysis"], "answer": "a"},
    {"question": "What is the insertion of External Oblique?", "options": ["Linea alba, pubic crest, and iliac crest", "Xiphoid process", "Transverse processes of lumbar vertebrae"], "answer": "a"},
    {"question": "What is the action of External Oblique?", "options": ["Flexes vertebral column", "Compresses abdominal contents", "Rotates vertebral column"], "answer": "b"},
    {"question": "What is the nerve of External Oblique?", "options": ["Intercostal nerves", "Thoracoabdominal nerves", "Femoral nerve"], "answer": "b"},
    {"question": "What is the origin of Internal Oblique?", "options": ["Lumbar fascia, iliac crest, and inguinal ligament", "Lower eight ribs", "Pubic crest and symphysis"], "answer": "a"},
    {"question": "What is the insertion of Internal Oblique?", "options": ["Linea alba, pubic crest, and costal cartilages of last three ribs", "Transverse processes of lumbar vertebrae", "Xiphoid process"], "answer": "a"},
    {"question": "What is the action of Internal Oblique?", "options": ["Flexes vertebral column", "Compresses abdominal contents", "Rotates vertebral column"], "answer": "b"},
    {"question": "What is the nerve of Internal Oblique?", "options": ["Thoracoabdominal nerves", "Intercostal nerves", "Femoral nerve"], "answer": "a"}
]
